Don't get involved in Hans' investigation.
Tell him to stop.
No, wait.
- Come on, let's go.
- I will protect her.
My dad saw the man in this video.
- And he knows him.
- It will make my investigation easier.
- Come on, let's see him.
- You can't talk to him, Hans.
Sometimes, people lack courage.
Courage to face their problem.
Sometimes,
the solution is right in front of us.
But we are dominated by fear.
Are you going to kill me?
If you were my target,
you wouldn't be able to talk anymore.
Is it because of this?
Do you think Liam and Joyce have an affair?
It's just a film.
My daughter and I are not
the kind of people you can fool.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Really? Maxine?
Joyce.
Maxine.
You know we have a problem, Liam.
Can you tell me the truth?
Are you just staying with me
because you know
my dad might do something if we break up?
I don't know anymore!
I don't know! I'm confused!
I just want to explode!
Sorry if you feel alone.
This is what I only got.
I'm sorry
if I dragged you into my miserable life.
I want to explode
because this is already so full.
This is full of things I never wanted.
Like our relationship?
But I don't think...
I'm the right person to make you feel that.
Hans, where are you?
Please talk to me.
Hans.
Joyce.
Love, can you give us privacy for now?
I'll give Savana a sponge bath.
- Surprise.
- What are you doing here?
I just thought I'd surprise you.
Joyce.
Dad.
- Dad, what are you doing here?
- You're so beautiful.
How did you get out of the center, Dad?
I'll explain later.
My dear, I need to talk to Hans.
Do you know where he is?
I have vital information
regarding his investigation.
Dad, you won't be able to talk to Hans.
- Why?
- I also have something to explain to him.
This is important.
This is more important.
Okay, Dad. You can tell me.
The man in the CCTV footage
we watched on Hans' phone...
The murder suspect in the death
of a constructor worker in Casa Fuerte...
That man's name is Lando.
And that demon only works for one man.
What are you saying?
There's someone else behind the murder?
It's Congressman Ramon dela Peña.
Lando is his right-hand man.
He does Ramon's dirty job.
How did you know all that?
I used to work for Ramon, too.
I regretted and paid for it.
When Ramon almost got caught,
Lando forced me.
They forced me to take the blame.
I became their scapegoat.
And I couldn't say no.
Because they told me...
they warned me that you would get hurt
if I didn't do what they wanted.
I will never let that happen.
They are evil.
Ramon and Lando.
And if I speak up, who will believe me?
Who will listen to
a junkie and an ex-convict?
Who am I to speak up?
Dad, are they the reason
you got separated from me?
Is he the reason your life got ruined?
We need to be careful, dear.
We need to be careful.
Don't worry, Dad.
We'll not be scared of them.
This is the perfect time
to use my position and influence
and fight for what's right.
People will listen to me.
We will expose how evil Congressman Ramon is.
Dad...
There's something you need to know.
Stay here for now, Dad.
I'll just let them know I'm leaving.
Liam...
Joyce.
Liam, I... I need to go.
I need to talk to Hans.
Is this because of what I told you earlier?
This is more important than that.
Joyce, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for all...
Liam, please. You have to let me go.
Please.
Joyce, are you okay?
Let's shoot this last scene.
So we can close the sequence.
I need to go.
I knew it.
She has something against me again.
Maxine, no...
Guys, let's pack up for now.
- What did he say?
- What?
- He said we'll pack up.
- Director Phil.
Maxine, I'm sorry, but we'll pack up for now.
Josh, I'm sorry.
What are we going to do?
- Okay, okay.
- What about clustering?
Check the clustering.
Director Phil...
Okay, let's do it.
It's just one sequence, anyway.
Joyce... Joyce, are you sure?
Yes.
Let's finish it.
Okay, let's resume.
- Okay, let's fix it.
- Wardrobe!
Is this Joyce's outfit for the scene?
- She needs to change.
- Double time! Hurry up!
Noted, Sir.
Okay, we have two cameras here.
Okay?
Maxine...
There. Your arm is locked on Joyce's neck.
And there's a gun on the other hand.
It's pointed at her temple.
You'll say your last line
in this scene, okay?
The line that says,
"You left Chito, and I took care of him".
Okay?
And, then, at that part,
you'll have your realization.
- They're intense, right?
- Yes.
So you'll beg her to let go of Joyce.
While he's begging,
you will have a change of heart.
And while she's faltering,
you'll now have an opportunity, Joyce...
An opportunity to escape.
When you escape towards here... There.
We'll edit your escape in slow motion.
And when you escape...
We need to see it in your face...
We'll focus the camera on you...
on your face.
Your face must show the line that says,
"You and Chito will never be happy".
Okay?
And while she's running, you'll call her.
- Go!
- Cindy!
Cindy! When she turns around...
Bang!
That's it. And then fall.
Fall in his arms.
There.
And you go down slowly, slow down, there.
And then, there's the blood squib.
There's blood there.
It will come out.
And that's it. Okay?
The scene is very intense.
Does everybody understand?
That's what's going to happen.
Everything should be precise
and at the right time.
All of it. Okay?
Where's the prop gun?
The one we prepared earlier?
Yes, Director Phil. Here it is.
[Gun Props]
Come on. Bring it here.
Go, give it to her.
Okay.
Is this a real gun?
Yes, but it only has blank bullets.
Yes.
That's better,
so you can really feel the scene, okay?
It only has a blank bullet.
When you shoot Joyce, it won't reach her.
So that is very safe and looks better, okay?
Come on, let's take this.
I want to make it clear.
I want Dad to be prepared if Joyce speaks up.
But I didn't know he'd tell you to come here.
It's too late to regret telling your dad, Via.
Now, what do you want me to do
with Joyce's dad?
Leave him out of this.
No one will believe him anyway.
I'll deal with him.
I thought we'd fight only because of Liam.
Now it's your dad against mine.
Sorry, Joyce.
You've been taking a lot from me.
Hey! Concentrate, everyone! Quiet!
Let's watch this.
I'm begging you.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Shut up!
You left Chito.
And I took care of him, Cindy.
I did!
Sofia... I'm begging you, put that down!
Cindy has nothing to do with this!
Did you just use me, Chito?
You only fooled me?
That's not true.
Chito, I love you so much.
And I can't bear losing you.
So please, don't leave me.
Cindy!
Sofia.
Cut!
Good take.
Lovely. Perfect!
Joyce, get up.
Joyce, we're done, Joyce. It's a good take.
Joyce, we had a good take.
I'll take care of everything here.
You can go home.
Joyce.
Joyce, get up.
Joyce... Joyce... get up, Joyce.
Joyce... get up.
Joyce...
Hold on.
This is not fake blood.
Joyce... Joyce... what's going on, Joyce?
Joyce, Joyce!
Call a medic!
Joyce...
What happened?
- Joyce, Joyce.
- What?
What happened here?
What happened to my daughter?
I don't know, Uncle Edmond.
- What happened to my daughter?
- I don't know.
Joyce.
Ambulance!
We need an ambulance!
Call an ambulance! Come on!
Joyce, Joyce.
Maxine...
The gun you're holding.
Wait, they told me it's a blank bullet.
Where's the medic?
Joyce, Joyce.
Joyce, Joyce, Joyce.
Hang in there, dear.
What happened?
What happened, Joyce?
- Joyce, Joyce.
- Hang in there.
Where's the medic?
Joyce, hang in there.
Don't give up.
Hang in there, okay?
You have to fight.
Joyce... Joyce, we're in the hospital.
Hang in there, please.
Your father's here.
I'm by your side, dear. I won't leave you.
We'll get through this.
Joyce, hang in there.
Joyce... Joyce, we're here.
I'm here.
Doc, gunshot wound, right chest.
We'll need a closed tube thora.
Nurse, please prepare the extra beds.
This is arrested.
We need to perform CPR.
Please call Doctor Shin.
Excuse me.
Miss Via, how are you?
I came as soon as I heard what had happened.
We're here in response to the accident
that happened
in the set of Joyce Trinidad's film.
Yes, that's our film.
It suddenly got loaded with a bullet.
I never thought of testing it first.
What happened was an accident, Deedee.
- It's not your fault.
- Miss Megan...
Please calm down.
We will ask you questions.
Come here. Sit down first.
Please tell us what really happened,
so we won't have any problem.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16...
Son.
Son...
How's Joyce?
Joanne, our daughter...
T-There was an accident...
What happened?
Why were you at the set?
Did you escape from rehab again?
- Joanne.
- You escaped from rehab again!
Let's calm down.
The doctor is doing everything they can.
- What do you mean by calm down?
- They're attending...
They're attending to Joyce.
Calm down?
How can I calm down? My daughter could die!
What happened to your daughter?
You were at the set! You were there!
Your daughter got harmed!
I protected her. I did everything.
I gave everything as a mother.
I became a mother and a father to her.
You? What did you do for her?
You chose to have a worthless life!
I know you're hurting, but...
- You're right.
- What?
I understand you.
You're right.
Miss Via.
You'll be fine, okay?
I know it's very intense.
There's a lot of blood.
But please, relax.
How can I relax, Queenie! Come on!
Did you see it?
Did you see how Liam cried for that woman?
Did you?
Excuse me?
Miss, that woman... Miss Joyce is dying.
I get it. We're evil queens.
We were the princesses that were never saved,
but please, just this time,
your jealousy is uncalled for.
Miss, where are you going?
The police will talk to us.
Wait, Deedee couldn't have done
what you're thinking.
She didn't do anything wrong!
Maybe it's just a protocol.
I'll go with her to the police station.
I'll go with her too.
I'm the Executive Producer.
So I'm the one who should take responsibility.
The other people on the set
will be investigated the next day.
Let's go.
What happened to my daughter?
Madam, please stop.
Explain it to me!
- Son...
- Mom.
You have no right to talk to me
until my daughter becomes okay.
Does she look okay?
Look at her! Is she doing okay?
If something happens to my daughter,
I have no one else to blame but you!
You talked my daughter
into doing that small-time movie!
Joyce.
Dad!
What did you do?
What do you mean?
I thought you wanted to protect me?
That's how I can protect myself
from Joyce's revelation.
That's your way, Dad?
To kill?
Is that how easy it is for you, Dad?
Tell me, my beautiful daughter.
Deep inside your heart...
isn't that what you want, too?
To get rid that woman.
[2 hours before]
Blood effect... okay, check.
Gun prop...
okay, check.
And then, blank bullets.
Okay, check.
Deedee, are you finished doing that?
Yes, Miss Megan.
Okay, can you help me?
Okay.
[Gun Props]
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20...
Lord, I'm begging you.
Please save Joyce...
for the sake of all who love her.
For the people who are hurting right now...
who got involved...
Please help them.
And please don't let my son
take all the blame.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18...
Liam?
Joyce.
Joyce, please forgive me.
This is all my fault.
I didn't mean it, Joyce. Forgive me.
Liam, what are you doing?
What are you talking about?
One...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
I don't know where I'll be without you.
Me, too, Liam.
I'm also happy to be working with you.
But wait, where is this conversation headed?
I love you.
It's like a movie.
These things we see
are the real magic for me.
What if she likes you?
What if...
What's happening?
16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21,
22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27,
28, 29, 30.
What's happening?
Flatline.
Let's pronounce it.
4:46 AM, time of death.
Please tell the relatives.
No.
No...
No, no...
Hello, Miss Via.
Miss Joyce is gone.
No...
What have I done?
No.
What happened?
Answer me!
What?
Joyce...
This is a sad day for the showbiz industry.
Because we received news
about the sudden death
of talented young actress Joyce Trinidad,
more popularly known as Savana.
Miss Joyce is such a good person.
She's close to the kids in the orphanage.
The nuns and the kids who are dear to her...
will pray for justice and truth
behind your death, Joyce.
My God.
Why did you take her?
Why did you take her from us?
God, why did you take her from us?
My baby.
Why did you take her from us?
Joyce, Joyce, Joyce...
She's my baby.
My baby, my child.
Joyce, wherever you are,
the people of Verde Village are saddened
by your passing.
Society has neglected us...
but you treated us
with kindness and compassion.
Verde Village is your home.
We will forever mourn for your death.
While the investigation is ongoing,
the production assistant
who manages the props of the film
will remain in police custody.
Was it an accident?
Or is someone liable for the sudden demise
of the actress, Joyce Trinidad?
I should have died instead.
Miss Joyce, please wake up.
We still have to do TikTok, remember?
Miss Joyce, wake up.
Let's do TikTok.
Miss Joyce.
Miss Joyce, wake up.
Miss Joyce!
Wake up.
Sep.
Sep, dear. Come on. That's enough.
Come on, let's sit down.
That's enough.
Sir Liam!
Sir Liam.
Miss Joyce.
Sep.
Come on.
Why are you crying?
You know what, Sep?
Miss Joyce doesn't want to see you crying.
She wants you to always smile.
There you go. Smile.
Why don't you go inside?
I'm okay here.
I can see Miss Joyce from here.
Do you remember our conversation?
Miss Joyce is like that, too.
She's like a star.
Even though she's far away,
she's still watching over us.
So Miss Joyce is the same as my parents?
Is she also now a star?
She's the brightest star.
Sep, when you feel lonely,
all you have to do is look at the stars,
and you can talk to Miss Joyce.
Is she watching over us?
I want to be near my parents and Miss Joyce
when I become a star.
I don't want to be away from them.
And I will watch over you, too.
You're not supposed to talk like that, Sep.
It will take a long time for that to happen.
And while we're still in this world...
I promise
Miss Joyce, your mom, and your dad...
that I will watch over you.
How dare you come here!
How dare you!
Ma'am, please.
Let us see her, even for a while.
Let us see Joyce for one last time.
You're a mother, too, right? You're a mother!
You should understand
the pain I'm feeling right now.
Mom.
Mom, let's go.
I'm okay.
I'm okay now. I saw Joyce already.
Get lost!
Leave!
Don't you ever come back
to my daughter's wake!
Get lost!
You! You killed my daughter!
You killed Joyce.
You killed Joyce!
If something happens to my daughter,
I will blame no one else but you!
You talked my daughter
into doing that small-time movie!
Joyce?
Joyce, what happened? Why are you-
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Liam, I don't know if I still want what I do.
I don't know if this is right.
I'm not sure
if this is still the life I'm dreaming of.
I don't want it anymore.
Joyce, Joyce.
In the brief moment that I got to know you,
when I was still courting you...
I can say
that you're the strongest person I have met.
Liam, please.
Please, just this once, can I breathe?
Run away with me.
I'll go anywhere with you. I won't leave you.
Thank you, Director! Thank you!
Joyce...
Joyce, where are you?
Hey, Joyce! Joyce!
Come back here!
Joyce!
You killed Joyce!
You killed her!
You killed my daughter!
I dragged her into my mess!
Joyce died carrying that in her chest.
What do you mean, Uncle Edmond?
What did you tell Joyce?
There's no one else to blame but me.
If only I didn't go back to her life.
This is my fault.
What do I do with her cell phone?
I don't know the password.
- Can I borrow it, Auntie?
- How did you open it?
She asked me to exchange passwords with her
while she's still not returning my feelings.
So we'll be assured that there's no one else.
I love your daughter so much, Auntie.
I'm recording myself
in case something happens to me
because of the information I know.
Hans, I know you have access to my phone.
I know you can open this.